So i'm driving my car the other night,
那天晚上  我正开着车
And what do you think happens?
知道发生什么了吗
I crashed into a utility pole.
我撞到了电线杆上
Then, to add insult to injury...
更惨的是
I was electrocuted.
我被电打了
What can i say?
真是无语
It was one of those days.
就那么发生了
All my neighbors heard it happen,
所有邻居都听到了
So they quickly left their microwaved burritos...
她们很快放下了卷饼
And their expensive jars of moisturizer...
价格不菲的润肤霜
And their racy pay-per-view movies...
计费电影
And they hurried outside,
冲到外面
Excited to see what all the ruckus was about.
想知道究竟发生了什么事
But then, when they saw it was me,
她们看到是我时
This weird thing happened.
奇怪的事情发生了
For a moment, no one moved or said anything.
片刻寂静  大家站着不动
They just stared.
只是盯着我
And then...
然后
Oh, my god.
天哪
All hell broke loose.
大家一阵躁动
Does anybody know c.p.r.?
有人懂心肺复苏吗
There's been an accident.
这里发生了意外
Edie!
伊迪
Can you hear me?
能听到我说话吗
Yes, everyone suddenly became very concerned,
是的  大家都开始关心我
Which was touching,
这很让我感动
But ultimately pointless.
但最终还是无济于事
Moments before the ambulance finally arrived,
急救车到达之前
I heard someone whisper...
我听到有人小声说
Don't worry, edie.
伊迪  不要担心
You're gonna get through this. you're gonna be just fine.
会过去的  你会没事的
Susan mayer--wrong again.
苏珊·梅尔  又错了
Two seconds later, it happened.
两秒之后
With all of my neighbors surrounding me,
在所有邻居的注视下
I took my last breath.
我咽下了最后一口气
The good news?
也有好的一面
I died just like i lived--
虽然我死了
As the complete and utter center of attention.
但仍像活着一样  是大家瞩目的焦点
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
本字幕由人人影视翻译组制作
时间轴：桠桠  后期：孤帆
翻译：小小天  鱼公主  桃金娘银  校对：小门柴
Two days after i kicked the proverbial bucket,
在我升天两日之后
My husband asked my neighbors to do me a favor.
我丈夫让邻居们帮个忙
You could tell from the looks on their faces
从她们的表情  你可以看出
It wasn't something they... wanted to do,
她们并不情愿
But... they agreed to do it anyway.
但  她们最后还是答应了
So the next day, they piled into a car
然后第二天  她们聚在车里
With two thermoses filled with coffee,
带着两个装满咖啡的保温瓶
A basket filled with baked goods
一个装满烤饼的篮子
And an urn that was filled with... me.
还有一个装有我的骨灰缸
I hate that we have to this.
真讨厌我们要这么做
So you've said.
你已经说过了
I mean, it really is the kind of thing a relative should do.
我是说  这是一个亲人应该做的
Maybe it is, but we're in the car, on our way there,
也许吧  但我们已经在去那的路上了
So stop your bitching. well,
还是别抱怨了
can you at least put the radio on?
那你至少该把广播打开吧
I won't feel like bitching
如果我能跟着唱歌什么的话
if i can sing along to something.
就不会感觉有抱怨了
If you start singing, i'll start bitching,
你要唱的话  我就开始抱怨
-And you don't want it.
-你不想吧
it's a 4-hour drive.
要坐4个小时的车
We have to do something to pass the time.
我们要做点事来消磨时间
Here's a thought. why don't we talk about edie?
我有个建议  为什么不谈谈伊迪呢
And say what?
说什么
I don't know, but she is the reason we're on this trip.
不知道  但她是我们在车上的原因
Uh, maybe we could share memories or tell stories.
也许我们可以谈谈有关她的回忆
Mm. why don't you start with the time
那就从
She tried to steal your comatose boyfriend?
她试图偷你那昏迷不醒的男朋友开始吧
-That was fun.
-有意思
okay, i was thinking
我在想
Of stories that put edie in a positive light.
伊迪的一些积极方面的事
And after that five minutes is up, then what do we do?
5分钟就说完了  然后呢
The woman is dead, people. let's honor her memory.
她死了  我们尊敬下她吧
Well, i'm all for saying a few nice things...
我们都想说些好的事
But you were never really friends.
但你们从没做过真正的朋友
You and edie clashed right from the start.
你跟伊迪从一开始就势不两立
Yeah.
是啊
That's what everybody thinks.
每个人都这么想
But the the first time we met,
但我们第一次见面时
It seemed like we'd end up being the best of friends.
本以为是要成为好朋友的
Oh, that's disgusting.
真恶心
No, it's okay.
没啥
It landed on the detergent box.
它掉在了袋子上
Here.
拿去
You go buy yourself a fresh doughnut
再去买个新鲜的面包圈
Or booze, crack, whatever eases the pain.
或是能缓解疼痛的酒啊之类的东西
Just move it along.
把它扔了
Uh, you think i'm homeless. oh, no, no, no.
你认为我是流浪汉吗  不是
No, i live here.
我住这里
I-i can prove it.
我可以证明
I know exactly what's in this garbage bag.
这垃圾袋里我都知道有什么
Um, empty rton of eggs, coffee grinds,
空鸡蛋盒  咖啡沫
Shampoo bottle...
洗发水瓶
Wart removal cream?
减肥膏
You're right. i'm homeless.
你说对了  我是流浪汉
Susan mayer. oh.
我是苏珊·梅尔
It's all cleared up.
都弄干净了
Mm. edie britt. i just moved in down the street.
伊迪·布利特  我刚搬进来
Oh, yeah. i saw the moving van. welcome.
我看到搬家汽车了  欢迎
Thanks.
谢谢
So is it just you, or do you have a family?
你是一个人  还是跟家人一起
I have a son. he lives with his dad.
我有个儿子  跟他爸住在一起
It's a long story. i'll tell you one day over a margarita.
说来话长  下次我们喝酒的时候可以谈
You wanna invite me in for a margarita?
你想让我进去喝一杯吗
How about coffee? i just put on a pot.
咖啡怎么样  我刚煮上
Great.
好极了
You can fill me in on all of the neighborhood gossip,
你可以告诉我邻居们的事
Starting with the redhead across the street
从对面那红头发开始
With the muffin basket. that's a robot, right?
拿着松饼篮子  像个机器人
Funny and likes to gossip.
好  我们随便聊聊
-We're gonna get along just fine.
-我们会相处得不错的
yes, we are.
是的
Wait. stop.
等等  停下来
Could we just rest for a second?
能不能休息一会
We've only gone four blocks.
我们才过了4条街
Okay, i lied.
好吧  我撒谎了
I hate running.
我讨厌跑步
Well, why didn't you say something?
你之前为什么不说
We've been doing this for a week.
我们都跑了一周了
because we were starting to become friends
因为我们刚成为朋友
And you like to run, and i like to...
你喜欢跑步  我喜欢
Sit and...
坐下
One of us had to give.
我们中要有一个人妥协
-Hi, susan!
-苏珊  你好
oh, hi, helen
你好  海伦
I would have introduced you,
我应该介绍你们认识
But once helen starts talking, she doesn't shut up.
但她一旦开始说  就没完没了
-Right. ed told me that.
-是啊  爱德跟我说过
oh, you met ed?
你见过爱德
Oh, yeah. i've gotten to know him quite well.
我很了解他
Yeah?
为什么
We're kinda...
我们一起
Doing it.
做过
Doing what?
做过什么
It.
那个
Ed is married.
爱德结过婚了
Yeah, i'm a naughty girl.
我是个顽皮的女孩
No, you're being immoral.
你这么做不道德
You're committing adultery.
这是通奸罪
Actually, ed's committing adultery. i'm just getting laid.
准确来说  爱德是通奸  我只是找人上床
You know, forget i ever mentioned it.
忘了我说的吧
I can't forget something like this.
这种事我忘不了
Helen is my very good friend.
海伦是我很好的朋友
i thought you just said she was
我以为你只是说她
She is annoying, and i hide when she knocks on my door,
她是没完没了地说话  她来敲门我躲着
She does not deserve for you to be wrecking her marriage.
但你不应该破坏她的婚姻
Where are you going?
你要去哪
Home.
回家
Oh, so you're not gonna be my friend anymore?
你不再是我的朋友了吗
I don't think so.
是的
I thought you didn't like running.
我以为你不喜欢跑步
Well, it depends on what i'm running away from!
那要看我是否为躲人而逃
Hi. i'm the whore that lives down the street.
我是住在那边的小姐
Could i borrow a cup of condoms?
能不能向你借一包避孕套
A cup? are you sure that'll be enough?
一包  你确定够用吗
Look, i know that you don't like me,
我知道你不喜欢我
But i am here to do you a favor anyway.
但我来是要帮你一个忙的
I was out to dinner last night,
昨晚我出去吃饭了
-And i saw your husband with another woman.
-我看到你老公跟别的女人在一起
really?
真的吗
I feel bad saying it,
我很不想这么说
But if i were in your shoes, i would want to know.
但如果我是你的话  我是想知道的
You're welcome.
不用客气
Oh, i get it.
我知道了
So you feel i judged you, and for revenge,
你觉得我批判过你  然后想报复
You're trying to make me insecure about my marriage.
于是想毁坏我的婚姻
If i wanted revenge,
如果我想报复
I would have joined them and made it a threesome.
我会加入他们  来个三人行了
You know, karl would never cheat,
卡尔从来不会欺骗我
And the woman he was with-- brandi, his secretary,
跟他一起的女人是  布兰迪  他秘书
And he took her out for her birthday.
他带她去庆祝生日
Oh, the old "i'm taking my secretary
又是"我带秘书
Out for her birthday" routine.
去庆祝生日"的老路子
Hmm. nice tip of the hat to the classics.
编得真经典
Okay, well, since you're on this moral roll,
既然你想谈谈道德
Why don't we walk over to helen's?
我们为什么不去找海伦谈谈
And i will introduce you. we can have some tea,
我可以介绍你  我们喝喝茶
And then you two could swap stories
然后你俩可以交流
About ed's favorite positions.
爱德最喜欢的姿势
What i do and what brandi's doing is completely different.
我跟布兰迪的行为完全不同
How?
怎么说
I'm not looking to break up yone's marriage.
我没打算破坏他的婚姻
I'm in it for a little fun, some free meals
我只是找乐子  免费餐
And to help an unhappy man through his midlife crisis.
帮一个不快乐的男人度过中年危机
Wow. you're just a giver.
你真是不求回报啊
Fine.
行
use all of your energy judging me, ignore the real problem.
用尽全力来批判我吧  忽略现实问题
But let me tell you something.
我来跟你说吧
This is my area of expertise,
这方面是我的特长
And i saw the look in that woman's eyes.
我看到那女人的眼睛
She's not in it for the free meals. she's in it for keeps.
她不是找免费餐的  她要永久占有
You should leave now.
你该走了
You know, susan,
苏珊  你知道吗
I'm trying to help my neighbor out.
我喜欢帮邻居摆脱苦海
I thought it was the moral thing to do.
我认为那是道义上应该做的事
Three weeks later, i found brandi's bra
三周后  我在卡尔的汽车杂物箱里发现了
In karl's glove compartment, and, well, you know the rest.
布兰迪的内衣  你们都知道接下来的事了
Say what you want about edie, she really understood men.
看到了吧  伊迪真的很了解男人
I should hope so. after all those years of research...
在这么多年的研究之后  她应该了解
I can't help thinking about all the times edie
我忍不住想伊迪和我一起度过的
and i sniped at each other.
相互抨击的时光
We could have been good friends.
我们本来可以成为好朋友的
Well, if she knew what you're about to do for her,
如果她知道你将为她做的事的话
She'd forgive you for everything.
她过去什么事都会一笔勾消的
Okay, my hour's up. someone else hold edie now.
我的时间到了  谁来拿着伊迪
Mm. i'll take her.
我来拿着吧
Kinda looks like cat litter.
看起来像是猫的粪便
Lynette, don't look at edie.
勒奈特  不要看着伊迪
Or what, i'll turn to stone? she's all rough and gritty.
怎么  我会变成石头吗  她又坚韧又狂野
Uh, gaby, before we learn what edie tastes like...
加布  在我们尝到伊迪是什么味道前
I got it.
我来拿
I think a little more reverence for the dead is in order.
我认为好好拿着是对死者的一点点尊敬
Oh, please. we're talking about edie.
拜托  我们在谈论伊迪
A little more irreverence is what we need.
我们需要一点点不敬
Give it.
给我
Do you remember you took turns driving me to chemo?
你们几个还记得轮流带我去化疗吗
Well, none of you did it like edie.
没有一个人像伊迪那样
Hey, lynette.
勒奈特
How you feelin'?
感觉怎么样
Eh, same.
还那样
Well, here's the dvd you asked for.
这是你要的DVD
Thanks. i'll watch it during chemo if i'm not too tired.
谢谢  如果化疗的时候不太累我会看
Here we go
饭来了
Oh, hi, edie.
伊迪  你好
Hi. ugh. what is that?
那是什么
It's a health shake of fermented brown rice,
这是一种健康的发酵粗米汁
And for her entry,
为了让她好入口
A salad of radish, burdock root and bok choy.
还有萝卜  牛蒡根和小白菜沙拉
Mmm. what's for dessert, waterboarding?
那水刑官  甜点吃什么呢
Thanks.
谢谢
I can't get comfortable.
我这么坐不舒服
-Could you fluff my pillows?
-能不能帮我松下枕头
of course.
当然可以
Well, i've got errands to run,
我还有其它事情要做
And i'll be back to drive you to chemo.
我会回来开车送你去化疗
before you go, would you put my socks back on?
你走之前  能不能帮我把袜子穿上
My feet are cold again.
脚又冷了
Oh, of course.
当然可以
Katherine, you have got stuff to do.
凯瑟琳  你有其它事情要做
Why don't i take her to chemo?
让我来带她去化疗吧
It's fine.
我没关系
Okay.
好吧
See you tomorrow then.
明天见
Bye.
再见
Okay, where's your coat?
你外套在哪
Why? Chemo's not until 5.
怎么了  5点才开始化疗
Yeah, i've gotta make a little stop on the way.
我中间要停一下
Edie! whoo!
伊迪
Been here before?
你来过这
A couple of times. you're gonna love it. hey!
来过几次  你会喜欢的
Love it? i have cancer.
喜欢  我有癌症
I probably shouldn't even use
也许我根本就不能用
the ladies' room
女厕所
Oh, there isn't a ladies' room, so that's not a problem.
没有女厕所  所以那不是个问题
Um, i...
我
Edie, i have chemo in half an hour.
伊迪  我半小时内就要做化疗
Fine. then we better start drinking.
行  那么我们最好先喝两杯
i'm not supposed to drink.
我不能喝酒
And they're not supposed to do tattoos in the kitchen,
他们也不能在厨房里纹身的
But i have a bald eagle on my ass that says otherwise.
但我说行就行
Two tequila shooters!
两杯龙舌兰酒
- Hey, Edie!
-你好  伊迪
Reggie! oh, I thought you were in florida.
瑞吉  我以为你在佛罗里达
Nah. That was just a body they identified as me.
没有  他们把一具尸体当成我了
Oh. Reggie, this is my friend Lynette.
瑞吉  这是我朋友  勒奈特
I'm trying to cheer her up a little.
我想帮她振奋一下精神
Right on. you wanna shoot some stick?
你想来两杆吗
No, thanks.
不用  谢谢
Oh, come on. You can totally take him.
来吧  你肯定能赢他
No, I can't. uh, see? Cancer.
不  我不能  看见了吧  我有癌症
Oh. No sweat.
不用担心
I'll play you one-handed.
我可以让你一只手
Can you excuse us for one second?
能让我们单独聊一下吗
-I need to go to chemo. I have
-我得去化疗了  我有
Cancer. yeah, I heard.
癌症  我知道
And what do you want from me?
你到底想让我干什么
I want you to fluff your own pillows.
我想让你振奋精神
You need to start fighting this thing.
你要开始跟病魔斗争
I'm doing the best I can.
我已经尽我最大努力在做了
Oh, not even close.
根本没有
Hell, Lynette, you are the strongest person I know.
得了吧  勒奈特  你是我认识的最坚强的人
You're even stronger than me, and that's saying something.
你比我还坚强  你有能力做到
Now...
现在
I may be a little out of line bringing you here,
我把你带到这  可能有点离谱
But you need to remember who you are.
但是你要记住你是谁
Screw cancer.
让癌症去死吧
You are Lynette Scavo.
你是勒奈特·斯加沃
Two tequilas.
两杯龙舌兰酒
Now... where's that one-armed friend of yours?
现在  你那个一只手的朋友去哪了
I'm--wanna shoot some stick.
我想要来几杆
Wow. it sounds like she gave you just what you needed.
看来她给了你需要的
-Good for Edie.
-伊迪干得不错
She never let me forget it either.
她总是提醒我这点
She always insisted
她坚持说
It was the tequila shooters that killed the cancer.
是龙舌兰酒消灭了癌细胞
Oh, what the hell is that?
该死  怎么了
Oh, not now. We have a flat.
不是吧  我们有个备胎
Maybe it's a sign we're not supposed to do this today.
也许是个预示  今天不适宜去
Nice try.
得了吧
We don't have time for this.
我们没时间了
Anybody know how to change a tire?
有人会换轮胎吗
You want to hand me that cross wrench?
给我那个十字扳手
do you wanna tell what it is.
你得告诉那是什么东西
It's the t-shaped dealie
T型的工具
I'm gonna whack you with if you don't hand it over.
如果你不给我拿过来  我就用它打你
You know, Edie used to live around here
伊迪从紫藤郡搬走后
When she moved away from wisteria lane.
她就住在这附近
You mean when you gals gave her the boot.
你是指  你们一起骂她把她赶走的时候
Less yakkin more draggin
别抱怨  赶快弄
Bree, how did you know where she lived?
布里  你怎么知道她住哪
Um, I ran into her once, unexpectedly...
我有一次意外地碰到她
In a place I never thought I'd be.
在一个我从来没想过要去的地方
Bree hodge.
布里·霍吉
Follow me. I'll get you situated,
跟我来  我给你找个座
And I'll bring your husband in.
然后再把你丈夫带过来
Is that the visitors' room?
这就是访客室吗
Yeah. Why?
是啊  怎么了
You don't happen to have a private room, do you?
你们难道没有更私密的房间吗
You mean, like an upgrade,
你是指  像个高级房
Something with a couch and softer lighting?
有沙发  柔和灯光
That would be lovely.
那样比较好
Oh. you were being sarcastic.
哦  你在讽刺我
Yes, ma'am. Are you ready to--
是的  夫人  你准备好了
Oh, not, uh, just yet.
不  还没
It's not a bad idea, having an upgrade available.
如果能有个高级房间  也不是个坏主意
I bet that's a perk people would be willing to pay for.
我打赌这是个大家愿意付钱的特殊待遇
Ma'am, it's a prison.
夫人  这是监狱
The only perk we offer is a cavity search.
我们能提供的特殊待遇只有查蛀牙
To be honest, I-I'm not feeling up to this.
老实说  我不太能接受
I'm gonna have to come back another day.
我还是改天再来吧
Fine. He's got another visitor scheduled anyway,
好  反正他还有一个已经预约好的访客
So I don't even have to tell him you were here.
所以我至少不用告诉他你来过了
Another visitor? Who?
另外的访客  谁
Some lady. She visits him every week.
一位女士  每周都来看他
Every week? What's her name?
每周吗  她叫什么名字
I can't give you that.
不能告诉你
If she's visiting my husband,
如果她一直来看我的丈夫
I think I have a right to know
我想我有权利知道
Ma'am, I'm sorry, but I cannot give you her name.
夫人  抱歉  不能告诉你她的名字
Really?
是吗
Because i would consider that a perk worth paying for.
因为我认为这是一个值得花钱的特殊待遇
Well, well.
看谁来了
What are you doing here?
你来干什么
I wanted to see you.
我想来看你
And you didn't bring muffins?
你没带着松饼吗
It isn't that kind of visit.
不是那种看访
No muffins, no small talk.
没有松饼  没有应酬
Should I be scared or grateful?
我是应该害怕  还是表示感激
I stopped by the prison today.
我今天去监狱了
The guard tells me you've been visiting orson--
守卫跟我说你一直在探望奥森
Sometimes twice a week, she said.
她还说  有时一周两次
Oh. who knew lady prison guards could be so chatty?
没想到监狱女守卫这么八卦
What are you up to, Edie?
你想干什么  伊迪
I'm not up to anything, you redheaded ice cube.
没想干什么  你这红头发的冷酷的人
He's 15 minutes away.
他离我就15分钟车程
And quite frankly, I feel sorry for him.
坦白说  我替他难过
After all, I know what it's like to be exiled from suburbia.
毕竟  我知道被紫藤街流放是什么感觉
So you're not...
所以你不是
Trying to start up something?
不是想挑起什么事端吗
He's in jail.
他在监狱
My boobs are impressive, but they can't bend iron bars.
我的胸部是很诱人  但是也穿不过监狱铁窗
Thank you for... checking in on him
谢谢你一直去看他
And for answering my question.
也谢谢你回答我的疑问
I have a question.
我倒有个问题
Why aren't you visiting him?
你为什么不去看他
Oh, well, my schedule is just unreal,
我的时间有点紧张
What with the catering company and lookinafter benjamin.
我有酒席承办公司的工作  我还要照顾本杰明
Yeah, well, we're all busy.
看来我们都很忙
Come on.
得了吧
Why haven't you been to see him?
你为什么还不去看他
That jail is...
那监狱
It's disgusting.
让我恶心
All those men in cages, like animals.
关在铁笼的男人们  就像野兽一样
Even to step foot in that place is humiliating.
甚至踏入那个地方  都让我觉得羞耻
That man went to jail for you.
你丈夫是为了你才进了监狱
Do you have any idea how much he must love you?
你知不知道  他要有多爱你  才能做到这步
I do.
我知道
Then why can't you suck it up
那你为什么不能忍一忍
once a month and going inside and say hi
每月抽出一天  进去看看他
Try to help him get through this living nightmare.
帮他度过这段艰难日子
Why can't you do that?
你为什么不能做到
Now as I think about it,
我现在想想
Don't visit him.
你还是别去了
He can do so much better than you.
他能做的比你好多了
So... how are you doing?
所以  你怎么样
How do you think?
你觉得呢
You're right. I shouldn't have asked.
你是对的  我不应该问
I know it's horrible here.
我知道这很可怕
How would you know?
你怎么会知道
You've never been.
你又没进来过
You have every right to hate me.
你有理由恨我
There's no need to be melodramatic.
不用演戏
I meant for asking you to come here,
我是指  坚持让你到这来
For insisting you turn yourself in.
坚持让你自首
Oh. now that I see this place,
现在我看到这个鬼地方了
I don't know what I were thinking
我不知道我当时是怎么想的
You were thinking
你当时认为
I needed to take responsibility for what i did,
我需要为我所做的事情负起责任
And you were right.
你是对的
But still, asking you to make this sacrifice and not...
但  让你做出这样的牺牲
Ever...
我却
Coming to see you...
从未来看过你
How can you ever forgive me?
你要怎么样才能原谅我
Just be there when I get out.
等我出狱
I never told you about that because... i was embarrassed.
我从来没告诉过你们  因为我觉得很难堪
edie britt shamed you into being a better human being.
伊迪·布利特让你觉得很羞愧  使你成为好人
That is embarrassing.
确实很难堪
All right, ladies, we're ready to ride.
好了  女士们  我们可以走了
Good. we got some ground to make up.
好  我们还有段路要赶
I was hoping we would be able to get there before dark.
希望天黑前我们能到
How do you think he'll react when we tell him
你觉得我们告诉他的时候  他会什么反应呢
how do you think?
你觉得呢
I never thought edie would be crime-ridden
我从不认为伊迪喜欢乱来
I figured she'd wanna be
我觉得她想要的是
Pumped full of chemicals and preserved.
身体里注满化学品  风干保存
Isn't that what she did for the last 15 years?
过去15年  她不就已经这么做了吗
My theory-- edie knew if she was buried,
我的想法是  伊迪知道  如果她要被下葬
Her true date of birth would be carved into a tombstone
她真实的出生日期就要被刻到墓碑上
For all the world to see.
全世界的人就都知道了
you really think she spent a lot of time
你认为她真的会花那么多时间来
Thinking about her death?
想她自己的死吗
Yeah, I do.
我想  她会想的
I spent a night with her
我曾一整晚上都和她在一起
Right after carlos and i got divorced.
我和卡洛斯刚离婚的时候
Is this too red? I think I need something pinky
这是不是太红了  我觉得我要粉嫩一点
It's fine. hurry up.
好啦  快点吧
I want to to the club while this bikini wax is still fresh.
我想趁蜜蜡脱毛还新鲜的时候到酒吧
This is gonna be fun.
一定会很好玩
I can't believe we've never gone out on the town together.
我不能想象咱们从没一起出去玩过
Well, we've never been single together before.
我们以前从来没一起单身过
Oh, I feel so sorry for all those other girls in the bar.
我替酒吧里的那些女孩们难过
Oh, so do I.
我也是
To be fair, we should probably walk in backwards.
公平起见  我们也许应该倒着走
Oh, no, that won't work.
不  可能没用
We're an unstoppable team.
我们是无人能挡的
Mm, the hottest chicks on wisteria lane.
紫藤郡最火辣双枪姐妹花
Oh Be nice!
别这么说
There are lots of attractive women on the street.
咱们这还是有很多漂亮姑娘的
Like who?
比如谁
How about bree?
比如布里
Uh, with that hair color,
她那个头发颜色
You could stick a red nose on her,
你可以给她脸上再装个红鼻子
And she could join the circus.
她就能参加马戏团了
Lynette's beautiful.
勒奈特很漂亮
Mm, for a baby factory.
她也太能生了吧
-And susan?
-那苏珊呢
we're the hottest, okay?
我们是最漂亮的  好吗
Too much?
太过了吗
No, it's great.
不  很漂亮
All right. come on. Let's go.
好了  咱们走吧
Wow! You were right about this place.
这地方太棒了
Told ya. A lot of hotties, very few "notties."
就跟你说很棒吧  俊男美女很多
Ladies, this is
女士们  这是
From the gentleman at the end of the bar.
酒吧里面那位先生送的
Oh, and I just sat down.
我才刚坐下
Well, that's a personal best.
这就是个人魅力
Actually, the drink's for her.
实际上  这是送给她的
Oh! it's pretty dark in here.
这里面挺暗的
He probably didn't get a good look at me.
看来他没好好看我
Oh, Edie, don't take it personally.
伊迪  别当真
We're just different types.
我们是不同风格
You're right. some like tall, blonde and sexy,
对  有些人喜欢高个  金发  性感的
And some men like...
有些人喜欢的
That.
是这种
Now, now, edie. don't be snarky.
伊迪  别这么刻薄
We're both hot, remember?
我们是最漂亮的  记得吗
Although, apparently, i'm just a little bit hotter.
虽然看起来  我可能更漂亮
Well, one guy might think so.
一个人会这么想
One guy who's evidently intimidated
那个人明显是被丰满的女性的胸部
By full-sized womanly breasts.
给吓坏了
Hmm. yes, I guess I am a little on the small side.
我在这方面是小了一点
That's the drawback to having ones that are real.
这是真货的缺点啊
What are you talking about? these are real.
你在说什么啊  我的也是真货
Oh, edie, come on. when you jump up and down,
伊迪  你上下跳的时候
The room moves more than your boobs.
房子都震动了  你的胸部还纹丝不动呢
Well, someone obviously has a chip on her shoulder.
有人看来是怒了
I'd reach down and knock it off,
我能继续  击败你
But i can't go down that low.
但我可没那么低级
Okay, you really think you're hotter than me?
你真的觉得你比我漂亮吗
Let's just say that i have more of what men want.
我只能说  我有男人想要的
Yeah? well, i have a vodka soda here that says otherwise.
是吗  我可是有杯伏特加饮料  看起来可不是这样
Ooh! so he bought you one drink--
他送你一杯酒
A well drink, i might add.
一杯不错的酒
Well, it's one more than you got.
就比你多这一点
Are you saying that i can't get a man to buy me a cocktail?
你是说  我找不到人送我酒吗
Sure, you can, just not as many as me.
当然  有啦  只不过没我多
One hour.
一个小时
Whoever gets the most swizzle sticks by the end wins.
最后谁收集的调酒棒最多  谁就赢
See ya in an hour, loser.
一个小时见  你输定了
I know what boys like, we know what guys want
我知道男人们喜欢什么  我们知道男人们想要什么
I make them want me
我让他们渴望我
I like to tease them
我喜欢挑逗他们
They want to touch me
他们想来抚摸我
I never let them
我从来不让他们得逞
I know what boys like
我知道男人们喜欢什么
We know what guys want
我们知道男人们想要什么
I know what boys like
我知道男人们喜欢什么
Boys like
男人们喜欢
Boys like me
男人们喜欢我
Sucker
烂货
I know what boys like
我知道男人们喜欢什么
We know what guys want
我们知道男人们想要什么
Count 'em and weep, solis.
索利斯  数一下  让你伤心死
Well, i guess i could do that.
我以为我行的
Or i could do this.
谁知更行
I should make some kind of speech.
我本想说点什么
But think it's enough. we both know i crushed you, right?
事实很明显 我们都很清楚你输了 对吧?
Now if you'll excuse me,
抱歉我得离开了
Swizzle stick number 17 has a yacht and giant feet.
给我买第17杯酒的家伙有一艘快艇 和一双巨足
What the hell were you thinking,
你到底是怎么想的
Abandoning me at a singles bar?
把我一人扔在单身酒吧
I'm sorry.
对不起
I just needed to be by myself for a while.
我只是想  一个人呆一会儿
Why?
为什么
Don'tell me you're depressed
你不是因为输掉了一个无聊的游戏
Because you lost some stupid game.
而在这难过吧
I'm not depressed.
我不是难过
I'm surprised.
我是很惊讶
It's going by so quickly.
它可以消逝得这么快
What is?
什么
My youth.
我的青春
The harder i try to hold on to it,
我越是使劲去抓住它
The more it just...
它越...
Slips through my fingers.
在我指间滑走
And all the makeup and dim lighting in the world
所有的化妆品 和暗淡的灯光
Can't seem to stop it.
都不能掩盖脸上的皱纹
Oh, please. you're gorgeous.
拜托 你很美了
And you are going to stay that way forever.
而且你会这么一直美下去的
That's the tricky part.
鬼才相信
I'm not gonna be old.
我不会老去的
What?
你在说什么
Ever since i was a child,
当我还是小孩时
I've known that i was never gonna see 50.
我就知道我不会活过50岁
Oh, that's ridiculous.
真可笑
No, it's true.
这是真的
As far back as i can remember,
每当我回首往事
A voice in my head said, "live it up today,
我脑中都有一个声音 "活在当下
'cause you're not gonna have a lot of tomorrows."
因为你的日子不会太长"
You do realize
你知道
There's medication designed to get rid of those voices?
现在医学上可以消除那些声音  对吧
It's not a bad thing, gaby.
加布  这不是什么坏事
It's actually a gift.
这其实是一份礼物
I...
我...
Appreciate my life
感激我的生命
In a way that most people don't.
用和大多数人都不同的方式
I just didn't expect it to go by this fast.
我只是不想它过得这么快
That's all.
仅仅如此
Well, you know what?
你知道吗
I have a voice inside my head that says you're wrong.
我脑中的那个声音告诉我  你是错的
It tells me that 50 years from now,
它告诉我50年后
You and i will still be wearing dresses too tight
我们同样穿着紧身衣
And walking in heels too high
蹬着高跟鞋
And going to bars
去酒吧
Where we'll meet old geezers who'll buy us drinks
那些老家伙会用他们最后一笔社保金
With the last of their social security checks.
给我们买酒喝
If you say so.
但愿如此
Now come on. let's go to my house.
走 去我家
Let's pop open a bottle of wine and toast to our future.
我们开瓶酒  为我们的明天干杯
Why not?
走吧
Isn't that weird?
很奇怪吧
She knew she was gonna die young.
她料到她英年早逝
What do you mean, you two were
你们什么意思  你们两个是
the hottest chic
最辣的
She called me a baby factory?
她称我为  小孩工厂
Yeah, gaby, in hindsight,
加布
Maybe you shouldn't have told
或许你应该
that part of the story
省去那一段
I think we're here.
我们到了
So are we ready for this?
大家准备好了吗
I don't know.
我不知道
Can you ever be ready to tell a boy that his mother is dead?
怎么会准备好告诉一个小孩  他妈妈死了
Hey, travers.
特拉法斯
Remember us?
还记得我们吗
Sure.
当然
Wow. you brought the whole neighborhood with you.
整条街的人都来了
Did my mom come with you?
我妈妈也来了吗
We brought you some muffins.
我们给你带了些松糕
You can share them with your roommates
你可以和你的室友一块吃
Or maybe a favorite teacher.
或是你最喜欢的老师
What's going on?
发生什么事了吗
Is my mom in trouble or something?
是我妈妈遇到什么麻烦  还是怎么了
Come here.
过来
I'm afraid we have some bad news.
我们带来了不太好的消息
Your mom was in a very serious accident,
你妈妈遇到了严重的事故
And i am so sorry...
我很抱歉
But she passed away.
她过世了
She died?
她死了
When?
什么时候
A couple of days ago.
几天前
We've been trying to get in touch with your dad,
我们试过联系你的爸爸
But he's still out of the country.
但他不在国内
And your mom's new husband's never met you,
你妈妈的新丈夫从没见过你
So he thought it would be best if we told you.
所以他想最好由我们来告诉你
If you'd like, we could give you a moment.
如果你愿意  我们可以让你静一静
No.
不
I'm okay.
我没事
Well, i have a class.
我还有课
Uh, i'm sure the school will understand
如果你请几天假
If you need to miss a few days.
校方肯定会理解的
I don't need to do that.
没有必要这么做
I mean, i'm sorry she's dead, but we weren't very close.
我是说  我很抱歉她死了  但我们并没有那么亲密
Still, she was your mother.
但她是你的母亲
Technically.
血缘上是
But not a very good one.
事实她并不是个好母亲
Look, travers, we're all moms here.
特拉法斯  我们都是做妈妈的
We've all made mistakes with our kids,
我们都犯过错
And what we count on is when they grow up,
我们指望当你们长大后
-They'll forgive us.
-你们会原谅我们
My mom didn't even try to raise me.
她甚至都不愿意抚养我
I mean, she just handed me to my father and walked away.
她把我丢给我爸爸就走掉了
How do you expect me to forgive that?
我怎么会原谅她
Look, i'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I don't mean to be rude, but i'm gonna be late.
我不想表现得粗鲁  但我要迟到了
Hey! hey, hey,  wait a second.
等等
Travers, you need to know something about your mom,
特拉法斯  你必须更了解你的妈妈
And i'm gonna tell you. now sit down.
让我来告诉你  坐下
I'd only known your mom about a year
我认识她有一年了
When she came over to my house this one day.
有天她来到我家
Hey, karen! your porch light's on.
凯伦  你门廊上的灯还没关
sitting in your bathrobe drinking,
穿着浴袍喝酒
And you didn't call me?
居然也不叫上我
I kinda wanted to be alone.
我想一个人呆会
Why?
为什么
It's the anniversary of my son's death.
今天是我儿子的忌日
I'm sorry.
对不起
Every year i think it'll get easier,
每年我都以为会慢慢好起来
And it never does.
但从来没有
Nothing worse than losing a child.
没有比失去小孩更糟的了
In a way, you're kinda lucky you don't have any.
你算得上是幸运的  你没有小孩
Actually, i do.
我有一个
What?
什么
Mm, i have a son.
我有一个儿子
You lived here a year. how do i not know this?
你来这一年了  我怎么不知道
Because he lives with his father.
他和他父亲生活
When i got divorced, i gave him full custody,
我们离婚后  由他父亲监护
So i kinda know how you feel.
所以我清楚你的感受
I mean, we've both lost kids.
我们都失去过
No.
不
I lost a kid.
我失去了小孩
You gave yours away.
而你是抛弃他
And you have the nerve to tell me you know how i feel?
所以不要再说  你知道我的感受
I gave him up because i wanted to protect him.
我放弃抚养是想保护他
From who?
不受谁的伤害?
From me.
我的
You know, i tried to be a good mom. i really did.
我努力做个好母亲
But i know myself.
但我很了解自己
And if he...
如果
If he was gonna grow up normal,
如果想让他正常生活
He needed to get away from me.
他必须得离开我
What a cop-out.
你这胆小鬼
I think you're just being selfish.
我想你就是自私
You know, trust me, karen,
相信我  凯伦
There is nothing that you could say
我已经把自己看得一文不值
To make me think less about myself than i already do.
你没有权利让把我说得更差
But if it gives him a chance, it's worth it.
如果这样对他是一个机会  那就是值得的
Aren't you afraid he's gonna hate you?
你不怕他会恨你吗
I love him enough to let him hate me.
我爱他  爱到可以让他恨我
Well, i hope you're not making a big mistake.
我希望你不是在犯错
Me, too.
我也希望
So i'm not defending everything she did, travers,
特拉法斯  我不是在帮她说话
But you have to know, she loved you,
但你必须得知道  她很爱你
More than you can imagine.
比你想象得要多
I really need to get to class.
我得去上课了
Bup,up, bup. i believe i called shotgun.
让开让开  我要坐前面
God, she is so good at that.
天哪  她很在行抢位
She should be. she's been doing it
的确  她从坐公共马车那会
Since she rode shotgun on an actual stagecoach. hey. hey.
就开始抢座位了  不是吗
I realized... i never thanked you
我想我应该感谢你们
For coming all the way out here just to tell me.
大老远地赶来告诉我
That was really cool of you.
你们都是好人
We felt we owed it to your mom.
我们觉得应该为你妈妈这么做
Oh, my god. i can't believe we forgot.
哦  天哪  我们竟然忘了
What?
什么
We, uh...
我们
Also came to give you your mom's ashes.
把你妈妈的骨灰也带来了
We thought you might wanna scatter them somewhere.
我们想你可能想把它撒在什么地方
Unless that's a little weird for you.
或者你觉得有点怪
Why don't you guys take 'em?
我觉得你们更适合决定
Are you sure?
你确定吗
Yeah.
是的
You were her best friends.
你们是她最好的朋友
I'm sure you could think of the perfect place to put her.
你们一定知道撒在哪里最合适
Okay, we're here.
我们到了
Guys... wake up.
大家醒醒
Guys?
伙计们
We're home. get out.
我们到家了
Lord, lynette. you nearly gave me a heart attack.
天哪   你差点害我犯心脏病了
Yeah, i'd like to see edie again, but not tonight.
我希望再次看见伊迪  不过不是今晚
Oh, i think my leg's asleep.
我的腿麻掉了
Actually, that's my leg. get your hand off.
那是我的腿  把你的手拿开
Lynette, thank you again for driving.
勒奈特 谢谢你开车送我们回来
-You bet.
-不谢
hold it.
等等
We still gotta figure out where
我们还没有决定
we're gonna spread ashes
把骨灰撒在哪里
Now it's gotta be someplace that was meaningful to edie.
一定得是对伊迪意义重大的地方
Well, edie once told me she lost
伊迪曾经告诉我
her virginity in cow pasture
她在一个奶牛牧场失贞
If we can find that exact field...
如果我们能找到那个地方
We'd find a lot of traumatized cows.
我们能发现许多有心理创伤的奶牛
Do we really need to do this tonight? they're ashes.
我们一定得在今晚商量吗
It's not like they're gonna go bad.
骨灰是不会变质的
Fine. we'll talk tomorrow.
好的  明天再说
Oh, edie, what are we gonna do with you?
伊迪  我们该怎么做
Subtle as always, i see.
还是这么难以捉摸
This was a wonderful idea, karen.
凯伦  这主意很棒
It wasn't exactly mine. Now be careful. you're spilling edie.
不完全是我的主意  当心  伊迪溢出来了
Urn is empty.
已经倒完了
Let's do it.
开始吧
Shouldn't we say something first?
我们应该先说点什么吧
Like what?
说点什么
I don't know.
不知道
A few words describing how we felt about her?
说说她给我们的感觉
I don't think edie would want us to get all sappy.
我想伊迪一定不喜欢我们这么脆弱
Well, i think if we're quick about it, she'd be fine. mm.
我想她更希望我们能快点结束这一切
Here's a thought--
我有个主意
We all say one word that sums up what we thought of her.
我们用一个词来总结对她的感受
-And then we dump her?
-然后扔掉她
then we dump her.
对 扔掉她
Just one word. this is hard.
只用一个词  这很难
Okay, i got one. i'll go first.
我有了 我先来吧
Edie britt was sexy.
伊迪·布利特很性感
Perceptive.
敏锐
Strong.
坚强
Beautiful.
美丽
I need four words.
我要用四个字
Okay. i want to do edie justice, and for that to happen,
我想公正评价伊迪  为此
-I need four words, okay?
-我要用四个词
edie would so not
伊迪会
be surprised you're welcome.
不会很惊讶的  请便
Go ahead, susan. what are your four words for edie?
说吧  苏珊  哪4个词形容伊迪
One of a kind.
她是异类
Now it's time.
到时间了
And that is
这就是
How wisteria lane came to be my final resting place.
紫藤郡如何成为我永久的安息之地的
My ashes were spread over grass i had once walked on...
我的骨灰被洒在曾经走过的草地上
Beneath trees that had once given me shade...
曾经乘凉的大树下
On top of roses i once admired...
曾经欣赏的玫瑰花上
And beside fences i once gossiped over.
曾经跟别人叽叽喳喳交谈过的篱笆旁
And after my friends had finished saying good-bye,
在我的朋友们完成告别仪式之后
A wind came along and took what was left of into the air.
一阵风吹来  把剩下的带到了空气中
As i looked down on the world,
我看着下面的世界
I began to let go of it.
我开始释放
I let go of white picket fences
我远离那个白色的箭桩篱笆
And cars in driveways,
车道上的停车
Coffee cups and vacuum cleaners.
咖啡杯和吸尘器
I let go of all those things which seem so ordinary,
我远离看起来是如此平常的所有事物
But when you put them together, they make up a life...
但把它们组合到一起时  就成了一种生活
A life that really was one of a kind.
一种确实异类的生活
I'll tell you something--
给你说吧
It's not hard to die when you know you have lived,
只要好好生活过  死并不难
And i did.
我就是这样
Oh, how i lived.
我的人生啊